You need to enable javascript to be able to use this website.

   Roaming:   [Recover login](https://www.f-list.net/login_details.php) [Support Helpdesk](https://www.f-list.net/contact/)

Privacy policy
==============

F-List is committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of visitors to our web sites as well as the privacy of customers who buy from us. For visitors, we've structured our web sites so that, in general, you can visit us on the web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. For customers, once you choose to provide us personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), it will only be used to support your customer relationship with F-List unless indicated otherwise.

The F-List website conforms to the requirements of the Data Protection Act, 1998.

Visitors to our Website - what information do we collect?
---------------------------------------------------------

When you visit our website, our web server collects basic user information about you that includes your IP Address, your browser type and version, your locally configured language and locale, and the pages within our web site that you visit.

We may at times also use cookies, which are small pieces of information that a web site can store in a designated file on your computer. Cookies allow a web application to respond to you as an individual. By gathering and remembering information about your preferences, the website can tailor its operation to your needs, likes and dislikes.

We may aggregate information collected from other Websites in order to better tailor our website and products to your interests.

Members of our Website - what information do we collect?
--------------------------------------------------------

When you visit our website and log in as a registered member, our web server collects additional information about you, including your email address, and any character information you may enter.

If you use our customer services ticketing system, it will also collect messages, tickets and attachments submitted via our ticket system. If you email us, our website will collect the contents, subject line and other information relating to emails you send us.

Purchasers on our Website - what information do we collect?
-----------------------------------------------------------

When you make a purchase through our website, our web server collects additional information about you, including product purchase and order history and payment transaction IDs. We do not store financial information (credit card numbers, CVV code, etc) for any reason.

Visitors from advertisements on other websites - what information do we collect?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

When you click on an advertisement for F-List on another website, our web server collects additional information about you, including the name of the website you were visiting, the URL of the page you were viewing before clicking on the advertisement, and the content of the advertisement you clicked on. We may also collect information regarding how many times an advertisement was shown to you before you clicked on it.

How is information collected?
-----------------------------

Information is collected via the following methods:

* Information gathered from browsing our website
* Information submitted when you register for a F-List account
* Information submitted when you contact us via our ticket system
* Information submitted when you send us an email
* Information gathered from advertising publishers via ‘inbound links’, when you visit our website by clicking on an advertisement on another website

Who do we share data with, and why?
-----------------------------------

We share data for the purpose of providing our services to you.

### Payment Providers

We share your name, email address, billing address, financial information including credit card information (we do not store this ourselves), your order number and the value of your order with our payment providers. We do this in order to process payment for your order.

### Advertising providers

We share your IP address with our advertising providers. We do this in order to facilitate the processing of advertising commission payments, and to serve geographically targeted adverts on other website. Important note: This information is not shared with websites upon which adverts are displayed; it’s shared only with the advertising network.

### When would we disclose this information?

We may disclose this information in order to perform the tasks listed above in ‘Who do we share data with, and why?’.

We will not disclose customer personal and account information to others, unless we have reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, make contact with, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing harm or interfering with the rights or property of F-List, our customers, or others, or where F-List has a good faith belief that the law requires such disclosure.

F-List also will not, except for reasons stated below, disclose to third parties personally identifiable information. The circumstances under which F-List will disclose such personally identifiable information are when:

* It is necessary in order to provide service to the customer;
* It is necessary to protect the legitimate interests of F-List and its customers;
* It is required to cooperate with interception orders, warrants, or other legal process that F-List determines in its sole discretion to be valid and enforceable;
* It is necessary to provide to a law enforcement agency when the contents are inadvertently obtained by F-List and appear to pertain to the commission of a crime.

What do we use this information for?
------------------------------------

We use this information for a number of purposes, including generating statistics and reports on website activity and improving our website. We use it for the purposes of marketing, improving the content and relevancy of our advertisements, and tailoring the content of our website to your interests.

Third Party Bots & Services
---------------------------

F-List allows third party developers to build a multitude of applications such as chat bots, external tools, and alternative chat clients. Third-party bots, tools, or services are not affiliated with or controlled by F-List staff. While you, the user, may utilize these services at your sole discretion, the developers of these services or applications must respect user privacy per protocol found [here](https://wiki.f-list.net/F-Chat_Protocol) and policy [here](https://wiki.f-list.net/Code_of_Conduct#Bots).

### Additionally, the following apply:

* Third-party bots and other services may not store, transmit, upload, log, or otherwise tamper with user credentials.
* If a third-party bot or service collects other information about the user, such as character names, messages, or other activity logs this information must be disclosed publicly.
* If a third-party bot or service does collect information that is otherwise permitted, it is required to have its own Privacy Policy which discloses what information is collected, how the information is used, and how long the information is retained.
* Ideally, but not mandatory, the third-party bot or service should offer the following:

* A manner in which the user may view what information about them is being stored by the bot or service.
* A manner in which the user may opt out of the bot or service and remove their information from said bot or service.

**This document is subject to change at any time.**

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| ### Documents / Info<br><br>[Rules](https://wiki.f-list.net/Rules)  <br>[Terms of Service](https://www.f-list.net/doc/tos.php)  <br>[Privacy Policy](https://www.f-list.net/doc/privacy.php)  <br>[F-List Wiki](https://wiki.f-list.net/)  <br>[Browse Bug Reports](https://www.f-list.net/bugtracker.php)  <br>[Changelog](https://www.f-list.net/changelog.php) | ### Help<br><br>[Contact Form](https://www.f-list.net/contact/) | Copyright © 2009-2024 F-List.net  <br>All character profiles are **works of fiction**.  <br>  <br>[](http://rtalabel.org/) |
